<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<publication>
   <title>MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Application for SAM 9X7 Family</title>
   <urls>
      <url>
         <loc>GUID-097DBF27-0DFE-4821-8C81-E0DCC8425525.html</loc>
         <lastmod>2024-08-07T07:08:36</lastmod>
         <title>1 Harmony 3 TCP/IP Application for SAM 9X7 Family</title>
         <description>The following applications are provided to demonstrate the typical usage of Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack on a hardware board with SAM9X75 and SAM9X75D2G device.Application ...</description>
         <urls>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-738E709D-0D02-4720-93FD-864AA61AF6F9.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:38:21</lastmod>
               <title>1.1 Berkeley TCP Client</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of Berkeley API to implement a TCP client that establishes TCP/IP connection to a web server. Description The Berkeley TCP Client application is based on MPLAB® ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-D948EAF8-77A8-4C6A-ABC2-B7AC2A641CAD.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:39:27</lastmod>
               <title>1.2 Berkeley TCP Server</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of Berkeley API to implement a TCP echo server on port 9760. Description The Berkeley TCP Server application is based on MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. The Harmony ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-A392265A-7E95-4240-A739-F600628D7ED7.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:41:05</lastmod>
               <title>1.3 Berkeley UDP Client</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of Berkeley API to implement a UDP client that establishes TCP/IP connection to a UDP server, on port 9760. Description The Berkeley UDP Client application is ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-60A957E4-F782-48E8-93E8-E19A7F7F298E.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:42:02</lastmod>
               <title>1.4 Berkeley UDP Relay</title>
               <description>The Berkeley UDP Relay application demonstrates the use of multiple sockets for sending and receiving UDP packets. There are three different sub-functions for this application:UDP Relay, which ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-A2226319-C954-4FBF-81CB-B64EA551F294.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:45:58</lastmod>
               <title>1.5 Berkeley UDP Server</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of Berkeley API to implement a UDP echo server on port 9760. Description The Berkeley UDP Server application is based on MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. The Harmony ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-216B10B0-B0BC-4B84-9560-507687B7C8AD.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:36:30</lastmod>
               <title>1.6 TCP/IP IPERF Application</title>
               <description>Iperf is a tool for the measurement of maximum achievable throughput of a network device on IP networksThe Iperf demo creates an application to run Iperf on target board and measure the network ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-175E9A5F-732C-4FBC-9D71-EF10D766B64B.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:32:16</lastmod>
               <title>1.7 TCP/IP TCP and UDP Client Server</title>
               <description>This application creates Client/Server sockets for TCP/UDP protocol, with application commands. Description The TCP/IP TCP and UDP Client Server application is based on MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-4884A0C7-8A1C-4607-A31B-9EEF38CA1E07.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:47:44</lastmod>
               <title>1.8 TCP/IP TCP Client</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of MPLAB Harmony TCP API to implement a TCP client that establishes TCP/IP connection to a TCP server. Description The TCP/IP TCP Client application is based on ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-4771C396-CD79-47F0-A02A-0269CE130DF7.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:48:37</lastmod>
               <title>1.9 TCP/IP TCP Client Server</title>
               <description>This demonstration is a combination of the TCP Client and TCP Server application.It shows the usage of MPLAB Harmony TCP API to implement,a TCP echo server on port 9760.a TCP client that establishes ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-92AB4710-503F-4CEE-8284-6F3AC6215674.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:49:46</lastmod>
               <title>1.10 TCP/IP TCP Server</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of MPLAB Harmony TCP API to implement a TCP echo server on port 9760. Description The TCP/IP TCP Server application is based on MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. The ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-EE28E678-93CB-4F96-8DF8-220A31AE9837.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:50:31</lastmod>
               <title>1.11 TCP/IP UDP Client</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of MPLAB Harmony UDP API to implement a UDP client that establishes TCP/IP connection to a UDP server, on port 9760. Description The TCP/IP UDP Client application ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-CAB07081-903B-41F3-B64E-3C54E062872B.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:52:33</lastmod>
               <title>1.12 TCP/IP UDP Client Server</title>
               <description>This demonstration is a combination of the UDP Client and UDP Server application.It shows the usage of MPLAB Harmony UDP API to implement,a UDP echo server on port 9760.a UDP client that establishes ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-C305F1D7-B9CD-4281-9CA8-09A3877860A7.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:53:34</lastmod>
               <title>1.13 TCP/IP UDP Server</title>
               <description>This application demonstrates usage of MPLAB Harmony UDP API to implement a UDP echo server on port 9760. Description The TCP/IP UDP Server application is based on MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. The ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-CE6F89B2-C0FE-4F9D-8D56-24A22FE72FCD.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:55:10</lastmod>
               <title>1.14 TCP/IP WEB NET Server SD Card Application</title>
               <description>The Web Net Server SD Card application creates a HTTP web server on Microchip evaluation board. The FAT FS File System is used for storing the web pages on an external SD Card.This demonstration uses ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-5DBE9ED6-CC60-45B3-BF70-7301E02A2D7A.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T14:56:54</lastmod>
               <title>1.15 TCP/IP WEB NET Server Super Set Application</title>
               <description>This application demo enables almost all the Application Layer modules in MPLAB® Harmony 3 TCP/IP Stack. It is also based on Web Net Server SD Card application. Description The TCP/IP WEB NET Server ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-ACA0101A-06A3-4E7B-93EF-7B7F986D8D93.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T17:46:28</lastmod>
               <title>1.16 TCP/IP WolfSSL TCP Client</title>
               <description>This application creates a TCP client with MPLAB Harmony TCP API and establishes a TCP/IP connection to a Web server. The connection can either be clear text, or encrypted connection with wolfSSL. ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-8760D388-80A7-4384-8EBA-D71A9C9C0EC4.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-08-08T17:48:44</lastmod>
               <title>1.17 TCP/IP WolfSSL TCP Server</title>
               <description>This application creates a simple web server, that operates with clear text (TCP Port 80), and with encrypted text (TCP Port 443). The Web server serves a sample page with the text 'Nothing Here' to ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
         </urls>
      </url>
      <url>
         <loc>GUID-8670F112-D806-419C-BE6C-E2A6F7A1293D.html</loc>
         <lastmod>2023-11-24T15:12:41</lastmod>
         <title>2 Appendix</title>
         <description>Using at91boostrap loader with Harmony3 MPU applicationsBuilding at91bootstrap project using MPLABXMPLAB X IDEMPLAB Code Configurator</description>
         <urls>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-9C50946C-10C3-4B04-9A50-42D09FD444ED.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-01-15T08:02:30</lastmod>
               <title>2.1 Using at91boostrap loader with Harmony3 MPU applications</title>
               <description>MPU Harmony3 applications are compiled and linked to execute from external DRAM memory that is available on the corresponding evaluation kit. This require all peripherals and clock leading to the ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-CC51F30D-C2F1-4F70-B1A2-EE5D618DD4B6.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-01-15T08:02:09</lastmod>
               <title>2.2 Building at91bootstrap project using MPLABX</title>
               <description>Open a console and execute the following command to clone at91bootstrap repository into a directory named at91bootstrap.Xgit clone https://github.com/linux4sam/at91bootstrap at91bootstrap.X Open ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-329DD925-82EC-45DD-8551-6F024BC99257.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2023-01-27T14:19:15</lastmod>
               <title>2.3 MPLAB X Integrated Development Environment</title>
               <description>The MPLAB X Integrated Development Environment (IDE) is an expandable, highly configurable software program that incorporates powerful tools to discover, configure, develop, debug, and qualify ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-FBAB7A5A-AA24-4557-9B2F-70999207D370.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2023-01-27T14:20:01</lastmod>
               <title>2.4 MPLAB Code Configurator</title>
               <description>The MPLAB Code Configurator (MCC) is a free graphical programming environment that generates seamless, easy-to-understand C code to insert into projects. Using an intuitive interface, MCC enables and ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
         </urls>
      </url>
      <url>
         <loc>GUID-0FB3F908-88EE-45CE-94F5-E97AF9049C9B.html</loc>
         <lastmod>2022-04-04T12:20:47</lastmod>
         <title> Microchip Information</title>
         <description/>
         <urls>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-7551DC67-D79D-4F0C-B56F-7B17E12400E0.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2022-07-05T07:23:16</lastmod>
               <title> The Microchip Website</title>
               <description>Microchip provides online support via our website at . This website is used to make files and information easily available to customers. Some of the content available includes:Product Support – Data ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-CDA512D8-0DE4-4672-8716-04CAC681CB38.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2022-07-05T07:27:49</lastmod>
               <title> Product Change Notification Service</title>
               <description>Microchip’s product change notification service helps keep customers current on Microchip products. Subscribers will receive email notification whenever there are changes, updates, revisions or ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-F05182E4-B102-4775-A746-1FF37F465312.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2022-07-05T07:29:30</lastmod>
               <title> Customer Support</title>
               <description>Users of Microchip products can receive assistance through several channels:Distributor or RepresentativeLocal Sales OfficeEmbedded Solutions Engineer (ESE)Technical Support Customers should contact ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-E8251634-7B15-4073-A103-5A5F128B8699.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2021-09-15T14:48:25</lastmod>
               <title> Microchip Devices Code Protection Feature</title>
               <description>Note the following details of the code protection feature on Microchip products:Microchip products meet the specifications contained in their particular Microchip Data Sheet.Microchip believes that ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-125F1A93-76CC-4BD7-BACA-01844FBD5F4F.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-06-13T17:02:57</lastmod>
               <title> Legal Notice</title>
               <description>This publication and the information herein may be used only with Microchip products, including to design, test, and integrate Microchip products with your application. Use of this information in any ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-21750586-F9F2-4E33-87FB-8F2994BF4744.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2023-08-23T20:11:43</lastmod>
               <title> Trademarks</title>
               <description>The Microchip name and logo, the Microchip logo, Adaptec, AVR, AVR logo, AVR Freaks, BesTime, BitCloud, CryptoMemory, CryptoRF, dsPIC, flexPWR, HELDO, IGLOO, JukeBlox, KeeLoq, Kleer, LANCheck, ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-07985EED-D525-413B-AEFE-78B563328687.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2022-07-05T07:33:24</lastmod>
               <title> Quality Management System</title>
               <description>For information regarding Microchip’s Quality Management Systems, please visit</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
            <url>
               <loc>GUID-02A694CF-88A5-4ADA-8785-7EEEC62D66EA.html</loc>
               <lastmod>2024-04-23T08:39:10</lastmod>
               <title> Worldwide Sales and Service</title>
               <description>AMERICASASIA/PACIFICASIA/PACIFICEUROPE Corporate Office 2355 West Chandler Blvd. Chandler, AZ 85224-6199 Tel: 480-792-7200 Fax: 480-792-7277 Technical Support: Web Address: Atlanta Duluth, GA Tel: ...</description>
               <urls/>
            </url>
         </urls>
      </url>
   </urls>
</publication>
